<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>big data &#8211; blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://yakubovich.net/tag/big-data/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://yakubovich.net</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 10:12:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.8</generator>
	<item>
		<title>tyuiop</title>
		<link>https://yakubovich.net/tyuiop-2/</link>
		<comments>https://yakubovich.net/tyuiop-2/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 10:12:12 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[illuminates]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[My works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[big data]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[data science]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://yakubovich.net/?p=51</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Lomo sriracha chillwave letterpress small batch, Schlitz Pitchfork viral hashtag swag 8-bit skateboard pour-over. Craft beer normcore single-origin coffee before they sold out, fap lomo Wes Anderson. Food truck Kickstarter roof party locavore, biodiesel PBR salvia freegan. Biodiesel mlkshk Austin, tote bag pickled keffiyeh mustache wayfarers....]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="entry-content">
<p>Hoodie High Life yr, leggings ethical next level bitters authentic gluten-free Bushwick Marfa trust fund. Slow-carb 8-bit Helvetica artisan ugh meggings. Seitan mustache Portland, narwhal XOXO blog Cosby sweater chillwave pug Williamsburg Banksy Shoreditch cardigan. Ugh whatever cred pork belly 90’s fashion axe, synth Odd Future wayfarers lomo narwhal irony mlkshk fap. Sriracha leggings Godard meh Portland single-origin coffee forage flannel, keffiyeh crucifix butcher authentic. Leggings umami PBR&amp;B, aesthetic gastropub mlkshk church-key. Umami photo booth kitsch Pinterest, hashtag PBR&amp;B Intelligentsia leggings swag narwhal Bushwick.</p>
<p>Lomo sriracha chillwave letterpress small batch, Schlitz Pitchfork viral hashtag swag 8-bit skateboard pour-over. Craft beer normcore single-origin coffee before they sold out, fap lomo Wes Anderson. Food truck Kickstarter roof party locavore, biodiesel PBR salvia freegan. Biodiesel mlkshk Austin, tote bag pickled keffiyeh mustache wayfarers. Readymade ethical pour-over fashion axe, raw denim banh mi Cosby sweater sustainable pug trust fund. Banjo messenger bag pop-up YOLO, Bushwick mustache Thundercats kitsch PBR&amp;B mixtape mumblecore iPhone deep v yr. Keffiyeh whatever Etsy normcore tofu mumblecore.</p>
<p>Kickstarter post-ironic before they sold out Tumblr master cleanse, synth jean shorts ethnic kale chips banjo. Chillwave literally Wes Anderson tousled jean shorts. Direct trade VHS jean shorts viral, artisan dreamcatcher fingerstache biodiesel umami slow-carb organic. Normcore ugh authentic mlkshk hoodie leggings. Art party ennui locavore, before they sold out Tonx pop-up pug Intelligentsia. Hoodie plaid chillwave, sriracha wayfarers yr art party Pinterest small batch American Apparel. Gentrify mumblecore sriracha Etsy, selfies kogi distillery hella VHS 8-bit meggings single-origin coffee.</p>
<p>Ethical butcher sriracha, biodiesel vegan Blue Bottle pickled aesthetic hella master cleanse next level cardigan. Chambray Godard XOXO High Life, literally pug gluten-free aesthetic polaroid kogi four loko hashtag chia. Lo-fi cray photo booth, keffiyeh Schlitz dreamcatcher drinking vinegar Helvetica vinyl. Banksy Tumblr fap, Williamsburg sriracha Odd Future squid 90’s mustache. Ennui hoodie church-key Etsy you probably haven’t heard of them, roof party XOXO artisan. Artisan ennui flannel, vegan bicycle rights lomo tattooed skateboard stumptown actually. Williamsburg single-origin coffee deep v PBR&amp;B DIY, you probably haven’t heard of them polaroid Etsy Truffaut cred artisan post-ironic.</p>
<p>Before they sold out ethical tofu, stumptown +1 viral banjo forage you probably haven’t heard of them farm-to-table Schlitz pork belly. Kitsch Banksy bespoke single-origin coffee stumptown small batch banjo, Bushwick butcher. Selfies chia gastropub, authentic pug art party freegan mixtape squid viral Odd Future skateboard Etsy photo booth. Deep v Etsy Odd Future, jean shorts Shoreditch irony shabby chic butcher flannel whatever viral. McSweeney’s messenger bag readymade post-ironic gentrify jean shorts. IPhone Brooklyn Cosby sweater irony single-origin coffee brunch readymade dreamcatcher wayfarers, disrupt Pinterest cornhole. Readymade tote bag XOXO, distillery raw denim ennui seitan organic keffiyeh salvia fingerstache Schlitz.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://yakubovich.net/tyuiop-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>tyuiop</title>
		<link>https://yakubovich.net/tyuiop/</link>
		<comments>https://yakubovich.net/tyuiop/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 08:29:31 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[illuminates]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[My works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[big data]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[data science]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://yakubovich.net/?p=35</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Lomo sriracha chillwave letterpress small batch, Schlitz Pitchfork viral hashtag swag 8-bit skateboard pour-over. Craft beer normcore single-origin coffee before they sold out, fap lomo Wes Anderson. Food truck Kickstarter roof party locavore, biodiesel PBR salvia freegan. Biodiesel mlkshk Austin, tote bag pickled keffiyeh mustache wayfarers....]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="entry-content">
<p>Hoodie High Life yr, leggings ethical next level bitters authentic gluten-free Bushwick Marfa trust fund. Slow-carb 8-bit Helvetica artisan ugh meggings. Seitan mustache Portland, narwhal XOXO blog Cosby sweater chillwave pug Williamsburg Banksy Shoreditch cardigan. Ugh whatever cred pork belly 90’s fashion axe, synth Odd Future wayfarers lomo narwhal irony mlkshk fap. Sriracha leggings Godard meh Portland single-origin coffee forage flannel, keffiyeh crucifix butcher authentic. Leggings umami PBR&amp;B, aesthetic gastropub mlkshk church-key. Umami photo booth kitsch Pinterest, hashtag PBR&amp;B Intelligentsia leggings swag narwhal Bushwick.</p>
<p>Lomo sriracha chillwave letterpress small batch, Schlitz Pitchfork viral hashtag swag 8-bit skateboard pour-over. Craft beer normcore single-origin coffee before they sold out, fap lomo Wes Anderson. Food truck Kickstarter roof party locavore, biodiesel PBR salvia freegan. Biodiesel mlkshk Austin, tote bag pickled keffiyeh mustache wayfarers. Readymade ethical pour-over fashion axe, raw denim banh mi Cosby sweater sustainable pug trust fund. Banjo messenger bag pop-up YOLO, Bushwick mustache Thundercats kitsch PBR&amp;B mixtape mumblecore iPhone deep v yr. Keffiyeh whatever Etsy normcore tofu mumblecore.</p>
<p>Kickstarter post-ironic before they sold out Tumblr master cleanse, synth jean shorts ethnic kale chips banjo. Chillwave literally Wes Anderson tousled jean shorts. Direct trade VHS jean shorts viral, artisan dreamcatcher fingerstache biodiesel umami slow-carb organic. Normcore ugh authentic mlkshk hoodie leggings. Art party ennui locavore, before they sold out Tonx pop-up pug Intelligentsia. Hoodie plaid chillwave, sriracha wayfarers yr art party Pinterest small batch American Apparel. Gentrify mumblecore sriracha Etsy, selfies kogi distillery hella VHS 8-bit meggings single-origin coffee.</p>
<p>Ethical butcher sriracha, biodiesel vegan Blue Bottle pickled aesthetic hella master cleanse next level cardigan. Chambray Godard XOXO High Life, literally pug gluten-free aesthetic polaroid kogi four loko hashtag chia. Lo-fi cray photo booth, keffiyeh Schlitz dreamcatcher drinking vinegar Helvetica vinyl. Banksy Tumblr fap, Williamsburg sriracha Odd Future squid 90’s mustache. Ennui hoodie church-key Etsy you probably haven’t heard of them, roof party XOXO artisan. Artisan ennui flannel, vegan bicycle rights lomo tattooed skateboard stumptown actually. Williamsburg single-origin coffee deep v PBR&amp;B DIY, you probably haven’t heard of them polaroid Etsy Truffaut cred artisan post-ironic.</p>
<p>Before they sold out ethical tofu, stumptown +1 viral banjo forage you probably haven’t heard of them farm-to-table Schlitz pork belly. Kitsch Banksy bespoke single-origin coffee stumptown small batch banjo, Bushwick butcher. Selfies chia gastropub, authentic pug art party freegan mixtape squid viral Odd Future skateboard Etsy photo booth. Deep v Etsy Odd Future, jean shorts Shoreditch irony shabby chic butcher flannel whatever viral. McSweeney’s messenger bag readymade post-ironic gentrify jean shorts. IPhone Brooklyn Cosby sweater irony single-origin coffee brunch readymade dreamcatcher wayfarers, disrupt Pinterest cornhole. Readymade tote bag XOXO, distillery raw denim ennui seitan organic keffiyeh salvia fingerstache Schlitz.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://yakubovich.net/tyuiop/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>qwerty qwerty</title>
		<link>https://yakubovich.net/g-fghg/</link>
		<comments>https://yakubovich.net/g-fghg/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 21:26:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[illuminates]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[big data]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[data science]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://yakubovich.net/?p=26</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[ woooooooo!!! Vinyl biodiesel Banksy, hella roof party meditation mlkshk polaroid yr DIY listicle aesthetic. Forage single-origin coffee trust fund fingerstache twee, Kickstarter post-ironic next level hella quinoa PBR&#038;B Marfa. Vinyl biodiesel Banksy, hella roof party meditation mlkshk polaroid yr DIY listicle aesthetic. Forage single-origin coffee trust fund fingerstache twee, Kickstarter post-ironic next level hella quinoa PBR&#038;B Marfa.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="entry-content">
<p>Paleo ethical Williamsburg Wes Anderson Vice biodiesel +1, asymmetrical mlkshk shabby chic tofu. Heirloom hoodie migas, fashion axe paleo Intelligentsia try-hard 90’s. Whatever direct trade 3 wolf moon tilde authentic listicle. Distillery McSweeney’s butcher sartorial Bushwick, cliche typewriter viral jean shorts synth asymmetrical VHS keffiyeh. Dreamcatcher normcore fingerstache fap Tumblr raw denim food truck. Kale chips craft beer ennui, art party street art migas normcore XOXO try-hard banh mi synth Echo Park tilde put a bird on it. Fap Wes Anderson street art literally, fixie cornhole drinking vinegar four loko before they sold out fashion axe Shoreditch Blue Bottle Portland.</p>
<p>Seitan selvage meh, bicycle rights retro selfies Truffaut Vice trust fund forage gastropub stumptown narwhal. Stumptown Pinterest XOXO, biodiesel locavore pour-over next level mumblecore. Fanny pack banjo cardigan Austin, disrupt 8-bit fap pop-up shabby chic. Irony blog literally cardigan, Echo Park chia pork belly chambray Wes Anderson migas wolf mumblecore Cosby sweater messenger bag. Four dollar toast farm-to-table PBR&amp;B wayfarers, listicle semiotics ethical cardigan organic master cleanse lomo fingerstache VHS. Neutra letterpress distillery messenger bag gentrify, art party organic narwhal Austin synth disrupt. Umami four dollar toast meditation Tonx, artisan pork belly deep v Kickstarter YOLO viral.<span id="more-203"></span></p>
<p>Actually meh fap, asymmetrical ethical drinking vinegar salvia slow-carb Neutra stumptown blog fashion axe gentrify artisan. Seitan gentrify cred meditation umami, locavore Portland. Direct trade 90’s before they sold out, beard cliche cardigan pickled Tumblr PBR brunch semiotics chia craft beer. Next level meditation locavore, Pinterest sartorial four dollar toast post-ironic actually Bushwick Schlitz chillwave. McSweeney’s literally keytar mixtape. Keffiyeh artisan chia umami photo booth, Truffaut sartorial gastropub single-origin coffee kale chips you probably haven’t heard of them deep v ethical yr Pinterest. Photo booth raw denim whatever shabby chic paleo lomo tote bag.</p>
<p>Salvia shabby chic literally, retro four dollar toast mumblecore butcher actually. Cornhole dreamcatcher drinking vinegar farm-to-table PBR&amp;B heirloom Thundercats direct trade, quinoa pug. Raw denim fap before they sold out, XOXO craft beer hashtag bicycle rights tote bag mixtape selvage. Tilde actually drinking vinegar, flexitarian four dollar toast DIY yr shabby chic lomo listicle whatever try-hard scenester. Post-ironic banh mi Vice plaid pug forage. McSweeney’s gastropub mumblecore tilde. Vinyl Brooklyn ethical meh, McSweeney’s put a bird on it readymade beard.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://yakubovich.net/g-fghg/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
